Hey, have you heard of Film Plus?
A simple, accessible and free channel.
Who doesn't like it?
Just as each has its lid, each
Orange has its half. Here at Film
Plus we have movies for everyone
tastes.
You can choose action, drama, romance,
comedy and horror. Whatever you want.
Watch it wherever you want, on your phone
mobile, tablet, computer or on your
TV.
Don't forget to subscribe to our channel.
Get your popcorn ready, sit down,
relax on the couch and press play.
Enjoy the movie.
Oh.
[Music]
Ah.
Maternal instinct.
It's time.
Happy Birthday.
Go ahead, make a wish.
>> I wish I was home with Dad.
>> Don't let the candles melt.
They will ruin the glaciation. Go on,
genial.
I'm not hungry.
>> But,
I'm trying to give you a party
birthday.
>> We don't have a party.
We can try to have a birthday
normal, please.
>> Whatever.
>> Very good. Great.
Well, in that case you have to open your
gift.
>> It's your charm.
>> Mm. I thought you might have it.
>> It used to be you and dad.
>> Well, now it's you and me. I thought that
so we will always be together.
>> I wanted an iPad.
Well, you won this.
Come on, I'll put it on for you.
>> I don't want it.
>> Pontelo.
So.
Let's play hide and seek. I know of a
place where you will never find me. No
we will play that more.
>> Then we can play outside.
>> You don't have any homework.
>> What if I told you that's all I want
no homework for a day?
Please,
okay, but stay where you can
green
and don't go into the barn. Ah.
He.
[Music]
When he disappeared,
I knew in my heart what really
had happened.
Since then I think about that afternoon every day.
the days. I repeat it over and over again in my
head.
I wish I could have avoided it.
>> Sorry about this.
>> No problem.
>> Just send her home at 4. Luis already
should be there.
>> Okay. I must accompany her.
>> No, it's okay. It's just crossing the street.
>> Let's play hide and seek.
15, 14, 13,
12.
>> Prat said he hadn't seen it, but the
the way he said it melted my heart.
>> At that moment I saw what kind of person
it really was.
>> Seven,
six.
Five, four, three, two,
a.
Ready or not? Here I go.
I had to protect my daughter.
[Music]
I had to prevent more deaths.
My husband
He was a murderer. No.
[Music]
>> Hi, I'm Kate. It's
>> Juliaatein.
I'll put you through to Julia.
Hi, Kat. I was thinking about calling you.
>> Yes, it's happening. I'm almost done.
Listen, Yulia, I'm calling you because I want to.
know if I can have another advance of
book.
Yes, look, the publisher has some
questions about all the progress that
you have been sending.
>> Julia,
>> I'm going ahead.
>> Listen, Kate, that's not how it works.
things. As I told you, we have some
questions about your job. It's nothing
serious. I'm sure your memory is a bit
slightly blurred.
>> Will I get my money back? Yes or no?
>> Unfortunately, I can't do anything
without further progress. If you work for me, I
I'll work for you. Okay? Listen,
I have to go. They're calling me to a meeting.
Bye bye.
Time?
In
Elizabeth
Go out right now. Oh.
[Music]
Time.
I'm sorry about your birthday, love, but
You have to leave right now. No.
[Music]
V.
I amazed you.
Mother.
I told you not to go into the barn.
>> Mom, you're hurting me,
>> mom.
What's happening?
I don't.
I left.
[Music]
Come in.
Stay here,
>> Mom. Just do it.
Don't make any noise.
Ah.
[Music]
I'm hiding here. Is anyone here?
I told you, stay here.
[Music]
Ah.
of
The
[Music]
¿Show
something?
>> I didn't think I'd heard anything.
>> The house is haunted.
Can
put games on your phone?
>> Oh, no.
Hey, I feel like
good thing he reacted like that before.
>> I know.
>> Ah, I love you so much, so much more than
anything on earth.
You know, we didn't think we could have
children. And when I found out I was going to
have you,
>> You've told me a million times.
>> How much longer will we be here?
By,
maybe it's dad.
No,
it's just H.
I got a call about a party.
>> Is everything okay?
>> Ah, yes, yes, I was just
Forget her. Yes. Fine.
Hello, little one.
>> V.
Hello, Hal.
>> It's a very pretty cake. What are you celebrating?
>> It's birthday once in a while.
>> Damn, it's true. I
I forgot to bring you something.
>> Oh, you don't have to You don't have to
>> You don't know that I actually think I have
something.
>> Hal, no, you don't have to give him anything. In
truth is you don't have to
>> What?
Here you go.
It's okay. It's my job to take care of them.
of the.
Ah.
Do you know I'm nine? No, you see?
>> Thanks, Jal.
Okay, go back and watch your show.
It seems like he doesn't like me very much.
>> He's going through a lot right now. We're
trapped here. She hates studying in
home and this afternoon we had to,
sorry,
>> Did something happen?
>> I don't know. There's something strange about this house.
She believes there are ghosts.
>> It could be.
The woman who lived here before died in
upstairs, alone, without family.
That's why it was sold.
>> Oh my God.
Listen, Kate,
>> there's something i must tell you.
>> What?
>> Let's talk outside.
Brad died
in his cell.
committed suicide
and left a note.
>> Well, what does it say?
Look, I don't have to tell you if you don't
want.
>> Dime.
Yes, I want to know.
Well, I'll get to the point.
>> He said
Kate, I understand now.
Understand that
You handed it over. Of course, you
you handed over that madman
He also said,
"Go, I love you."
>> Hey, that monster won't come back.
hurt you. Is that okay?
Alright.
>> Yes.
[Music]
Amen.
I told you not to grab this. To your
room.
>> Okay, now.
>> What? To your room.
>> I think I'm leaving.
>> You're not staying.
>> Now
>> you're trying to get dad into trouble.
You don't remember anything.
>> I remember everything.
>> I'm just writing a story. It's not about
your dad.
>> So, about whom?
Mother,
are you OK?
>> Bet, please, it's time to sleep, baby.
>> I'm not a baby.
>> You're right,
mother.
Dime,
>> Will Jala stay overnight?
>> He's taking care of us.
You'll tell dad.
Rest. Turn off the light.
Good morning.
Sorry,
everything is fine now.
for the bastard who left.
[ __ ] them
I'm so sorry
now. Brad,
Brad is
Yeah. Well, we're not going to be able to stay.
here much longer and I don't know where to go
we are going to go.
Understand,
[Music]
will you stay with me tonight?
>> Look, I have to
I have to go home, you know?
>> Please, I can't be alone with Bet.
No. And please, after what happened.
the last time and Carol finds out about it
new.
>> They
I need you.
[Music]
>> Stay.
>> Enough,
Enough. Stop. Good.
>> I see what you're doing and you know, a
10 for the effort, but
>> please
that you leave now.
[Music]
GOOD.
[ __ ]
Time?
[Music]
Mother.
Mom, what's going on? I think he's gone.
the light.
[Music]
Have you seen my phone?
No.
[Music]
V. What
>> did you take the knife?
>> What?
Hello.
>> Hello.
>> Mom,
What's going on? Come in, come in. Who
no
Mother
[Music]
six.
Five.
[Music]
Four.
Three.
What have you done?
Of the.
A.
>> Oh,
>> wake up.
>> Ah. Ah.
Where? Where is my daughter?
Where is Bed?
>> How does it feel not knowing where you are?
Not knowing if you are safe.
>> What did you do to him? Mom, Mom. See?
See? See? See?
It's all you have.
I'm going to kill you.
>> You won't.
>> No, no, no. Put that down.
>> She'll be fine
>> as long as you cooperate.
>> Did you understand?
It's been a while.
>> My God, you
>> just make sure it's focusing well.
>> I know how to record a video
>> good.
Don't be so sensitive.
Take her back home.
>> Okay, but how would I know?
>> I'll come get you.
>> Okay.
>> No, no, you can't take it.
>> I love you.
>> No, no.
>> I love you too.
>> No, no, you can't take her. No, no,
no no,
don't hurt her.
>> So,
you are not easy to find.
>> Mary,
Please. We're almost at Nxton.
but the journalists caught you
First. The police moved quickly.
Mary, please.
>> The police here are not that skilled.
Your boyfriend couldn't keep his mouth shut.
closed.
He went all over town bragging about
who had a great job, taking care of
someone secretly.
>> Why are you doing this? Are you
Do you know why?
Proof.
>> What do you want? What do you want me to say?
[Music]
>> You lied to the jury so you could get off.
You set him up, Brad.
No
>> it was you.
>> No,
>> you killed our daughter.
>> No, not me, no.
>> You framed your husband. You sent him to
prison in your place.
>> No, it wasn't like that. Yes, you did and I can
try it.
And you have nothing to say.
>> What proof
>> now i have your attention.
Let's start talking.
They are going to kill us.
No,
We just want to talk to your mom.
Alright?
>> Why are you looking at me like that?
[Music]
>> Because you remind me of someone.
You have blood in your nose.
[ __ ]
[Music]
>> May 14, 2 years ago. Do you remember?
>> No.
>> I think so,
because I do.
May 14th.
What do you want me to say? What do you want me to say?
say?
He walked home. Mary, you
you said i could.
>> But he didn't.
>> I thought I would.
>> It happened.
in your house while you were there and not
you heard nothing.
>> No, you didn't see anything.
No
had to go for his body.
He had to go for his small body,
go down the stairs,
enter the garage and put it in your
trunk. Don't you remember?
Time,
in,
come on, see.
Time,
come on, salt.
>> I'm going to find you.
>> When we had dinner at your house, we could
hear the girls playing on the floor
above.
No.
>> And you didn't hear her screaming for her
life?
>> No, no. I didn't hear anything. I didn't hear.
>> You lie.
[Music]
You planned it all.
You made us feel comfortable and
so you could get her away from us.
I didn't do it. I didn't do it.
Brad did it.
>> I don't believe you,
>> Mary.
He hit me. He would have killed me if I hadn't
would have gone along with it. It was. No
I knew it.
>> There's not a single bit of abuse in his head.
>> Oh, you did know that. Because I told you
you were taking.
Luis knows it.
That's why you did it, Kate,
to take revenge.
Brad died. Mary
committed suicide.
More blood on your hands.
[Music]
>> We don't have all night.
>> What are you doing? Are you turning it off?
Why? Why are you doing it?
I really didn't want it to come to this.
Mary was infatuated with her and
prepared. He wanted her. He said that if not
I agreed he was going to hurt me.
It would hurt Bet.
>> No, Kate,
>> I wouldn't do it.
No, please, no.
>> You weren't liked, you know?
We were friends.
>> I looked up how to do it on the internet.
Sorry if I do it wrong.
Ah.
[Music]
Come on,
come,
come.
You made me do it.
Corne was seven.
She was very beautiful
and happy.
It was everything to us.
When she disappeared,
I kept waiting for him to come back
home.
I thought that one day I would return and everything
would be fine again.
I was devastated.
Not knowing about her was driving me crazy.
loca.
You deserve that pain, don't you think?
>> Well, what were we talking about?
[Music]
Damn.
[Applause]
[Music]
[ __ ]
Gist
>> Kate,
>> No, I'm not Kate. Hal,
>> Hello, love. I'm on my way.
>> I called the station and you weren't there.
They didn't know where you were.
>> Well, I work with the program of
witness protection. If you
They would ruin it, you know?
>> How many damn people are there in the
protection program in Hansville.
>> Ah, well, you'd be surprised.
>> Don't come home tonight,
>> love. I'm not with her.
>> So, sleep in the car.
>> I'm going to freeze.
>> Let your girlfriend host you. She'll be there.
delighted, I'm sure.
>> Oh, come on. That's not it.
Fuck you.
Ah, all right. Good.
If you think that, maybe I will.
[Music]
>> You never took the stand. Why?
Mary,
>> What the hell are you doing?
>> We have a problem. He called the
police.
>> P6
answer. Over.
>> 416 answers.
No, tonight Hal will have sex.
>> Stay still, stay still. And
>> very good. Clean it.
>> Don't tell me what to do.
>> I wasn't the one who did this to him.
>> Kitchen,
>> Mary. If he comes back.
>> I know, I know.
[Music]
It's him. He's back. He's back.
Don't worry.
[Music]
M.
Now I got rid of him
or I'll kill him
and then to you
and then you see.
You understand?
>> Hey, I got your call. I tried
call you, but
>> Yes, I was wrong.
>> Well, I thought I'd come and see what you're up to.
GOOD.
>> It's late. Jal,
>> Are you okay?
Yes, I'm just tired.
I want to go to bed.
Well, you're right. Probably not.
you should be left alone.
>> Good evening, Hal.
>> Wait, wait, wait. Look.
I know this is difficult, right? But everything
It will be okay, I promise.
[Music]
>> Thank you,
but I'm tired.
>> Sure, don't worry.
I'll call you tomorrow.
>> Yes, please.
Okay,
Of course.
What was that?
>> Only v
>> he still hasn't fallen asleep.
>> No, she
plays with her dolls.
You know how much she loves her
dolls
especially the one you gave him
birthday.
>> Right?
Yeah.
I'm glad you liked it.
Rest,
>> rest.
Damn!
What does it do?
is sitting there.
[Music]
M.
Very good,
sit back down. No,
>> Mary,
>> Please, I did everything you asked me to.
>> B,
>> shut up.
>> Let's go.
>> What? No, no, I won't go with her.
>> I won't go with her. She'll kill me. No,
we will talk. We will talk.
>> I said no.
>> Mary,
It's okay. I can do it.
Fine. Just keep it.
>> It wasn't part of the plan.
She was also my daughter.
[Music]
Take the camera.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ]
Think J. Think, think, friend, think.
Okay.
[Applause]
Listen, station. Over.
>> Go ahead. Over.
>> I have a pretty messed up situation in
Grover Road. It's an assault on
house. Kidnappers, I think.
>> What do you think?
>> Just bring everyone here.
>> Where are you?
>> The Maquel house, idiot. We have people.
in there. Are they kidnappers or
robbers?
>> Hell, it's an hour's drive.
>> Send everyone quickly.
>> Things,
>> Hal, don't be a hero. Wait for reinforcements.
Move
fast,
move.
[Music]
Sit down.
Know?
When my daughter disappeared,
Mary
It was a disaster.
She is
broke into a thousand pieces.
She didn't eat,
I didn't sleep
and sometimes that was all he did.
So I lost my wife,
I lost my daughter
and I joined in
completely
in this case
in the small details,
but it seems that
how many
the more evidence I found,
they wanted to know less about me.
You know, I was a rookie detective,
but Mary,
Mary for the first time in a long time
believed in me. You were
to prison for this.
I will
together with you.
[Music]
You don't have to be afraid of me.
Your mom is the bad one. You know
what did he do?
She's a liar and she's mean to me.
She
[Music]
has hurt you.
Come here, darling.
What did he do to you?
It's okay, honey.
I'll take care of you. That horrible
monster will never hurt you again.
>> I want to live with my dad.
Dear,
your dad, he
is dead.
[Music]
All the evidence pointed to Brad.
It was easy to find.
They thought he was careless,
uncontrolled, his worst enemy. But I
I just started to see that there was a little
pattern
like blood on clothes,
in the dirty clothes.
So he killed her, took off his clothes,
put it in the laundry and didn't wash it.
That creates
>> the knife.
They never found the knife, so
He was so clever to get rid of the
knife, but not clothing.
>> I don't know.
your body
in the trunk.
The car in the parking lot.
They are so
it's so stupid.
[Music]
Now the crime scene.
the closet was cleaned.
They cleaned it meticulously
and then
arose
late, too late after his
plea agreement.
You were the one who handed him over.
and then it all made sense.
[Music]
You cleaned the closet,
You laid all the clues, you handed it over
and then you got your deal.
You set a trap for BR. Why?
what would that do?
Because you did it. All the evidence
They are there because I keep thinking about this and
in this and in this. I'm missing out
something because there is no no no way to
that this happened the way it did
you say.
It was me.
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it.
knew.
I want that
just tell me.
Ah.
step by step.
This is what happened.
Your wife was sleeping with me
husband in our bed. In your bed.
They didn't even try to hide it.
You knew it.
[ __ ] She's really got you tied up.
>> No, no
>> I wanted to kill her.
He brought her to my house. He acted as if
was my friend and I wanted to take everything away from her
her little heart.
>> So
>> you killed Corney instead.
>> Yes.
>> [ __ ]
You're going to tell me.
>> Why?
>> Because I need to know.
Forward.
>> The girls were playing hide-and-seek.
I played with them.
She went up the stairs.
I did it there.
A.
[Music]
Lists or not?
Here I go.
[Music]
Ah.
I cleaned,
I took the body to the trunk of the car and
I left it for them to find.
>> So Brother was innocent.
>> Yes.
God, no.
Please wait.
I just want to know
if Bet will be fine.
>> Good,
GOOD.
>> She's just a child. She's just
>> I really will.
I will do it.
I'll kill you.
[Music]
You're dead.
I'll kill you.
Get up, get up.
>> Quiet!
>> Wait, wait, wait.
>> Let her go. Wait, wait, wait.
Let her go.
>> J, dispárale.
>> She killed my daughter. She confessed. I have
evidence.
>> Things,
>> I have it all on video.
>> Disparée.
>> It's on the phone. I'll give it to you.
right now. Okay?
>> Dispárale, J.
>> I'm going to take it out and show it to you.
>> It's a weapon. It's a weapon.
What's here, Kate?
Don't look at it.
>> The girls were playing hide-and-seek.
I played with them. She climbed up to the
stairs. I did it.
I cleaned,
I brought the body to evil
>> and I left it for them to find.
So, brother innocent.
Yeah.
[Music]
Come with me. It's here. We have to
Let's go now. I know a good hiding place.
Come in. Come on,
Mary.
B.
[Music]
Hells,
this opens.
Hide there, go on.
Whatever happens, don't go out.
[Music]
I know they're down there.
>> Is that you, Kate? The real Kate,
>> Can you come find out?
>> I can see you.
That cold, cold blood.
You made me do this.
>> I needed to know. Now I know.
>> Let go of Bed.
>> You can go down.
>> B.
What did you do to him?
>> She doesn't belong to you.
>> I am his mother.
So come for it.
List or no?
Here I go. Oy.
[Music]
Do you know?
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh,
>> It's okay, honey.
>> Don't touch her.
Love,
Wait, Corny, wait. Ah,
¿A
where are you going?
It's safe now.
I'll take care of you.
[Music]
No.
By
[Music]
that?
>> Why did you make me?
You can't do that.
>> I was helping.
>> You promised me.
You promised.
You must keep your promises.
It's to keep you safe.
>> But it's my birthday.
[Music]
By,
what what did you do?
No,
no,
No, no, no. I'm sorry. You protected her for
above all.
>> You wouldn't do it. Why?
that
is she dead?
Are you okay, baby?
>> I'm not a baby.
>> Are you okay? We're okay. Are we?
GOOD?
We're fine. Everything's fine. We're
GOOD.
>> What will happen now?
They're going to take me away from you
and you're going to be left alone
and you won't do that again.
>> Why?
Because if they
if they know, if they
if they see that it is,
you have to lock it up.
Bet, you're not like that.
>> Yes.
>> You can choose,
you can choose.
>> But mom,
I can't be someone else.
Yeah,
I know, baby, I know.
By
what, baby?
Baby, why?
>> I'm not a baby.
>> That was for dad.
Everything I did
was
to protect you.
But
Alright,
Alright.
I still love you.
You love me too.
Ah.
[Music]
Understand,
are you lost?
Oh my God. Ah.
[Music]